if you had started
a venture career let's
say five or seven
years ago like you're
starting at a high
where venture capital is
like easy to come
by And then so
you had that waves
of FinTech for example
going to 2017 2018
2019 where it was
very easy to and
your fundraising cycles were
C to Series A
and so on and
so forth like they
can be pretty fast
Terms and were pretty
loose diligence was pretty
light you know and
you'd kind of get
away with a lot
if you're a founder
And some founders did
get away with a
right And so but
then you come to
the 2020s going into
COVID you think that
things are gonna get
bad No but things
got better for venture
know valuation is gonna
be more crazy And
we don't need to
talk about the reasons
for all of that
but it was like
up and up and
up and up And
then right now when
it's kind of like
rationalized I would say
or normalized to where
it's at right now
people are like my
God it's winter game
over You know like
everything is right But
again if you were
building companies in like
an even earlier vintage
there were almost no
VCs And if anybody
was an HR or
VC the are incredibly
bad right They look
more like private equity
terms